<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Academic</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>img/map[gravatar:%!s(bool=false) shape:circle]</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am Naomi Smorenburg. A 25 year old student currently finishing my Master Methodology &amp;amp; Statistics at Utrecht University. I also did my bachelor at Utrecht University, Psychology, with a specilization in neurobiological and cognitive psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interests&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve always been fascinated with the way the world works. As a child, my favourite tv program was &amp;lsquo;klokhuis&amp;rsquo; which is an informative program in which very diverse topics are explained. This also lead to my nickname &amp;lsquo;Wiki&amp;rsquo; (from Wikipedia) since I know so many useful (and useless) facts. This interests but sometimes also bores my friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I was always so broadly interested choosing a study was not an easy job. I finally decided to go for a direction that was not &amp;lsquo;beta&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;alfa&amp;rsquo; but somewhat in between: &amp;lsquo;gamma&amp;rsquo; - psychology. Since I was always quite strong in mathematics I thought that might be useful in statistics - that is part of all social sciences. Four years later I actually chose to do a research master entirely devoted to statistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in the small city of Elspeet right in the middle of the Veluwe. We always had a lot of animals and people used to ask if I my parents were farmers (they are not, in fact). My parents just had a love for, especially horses, and moved to the countryside because of them.  Growing up on the countryside had the big advantage we would spent most our time playing outdoors, and I spent a lot of time at our neighbours, who were actually real farmers. When I was around 8 years old I got my very first pony, a black shetland pony called Famke. Although Famke was not a huge success after all, also I was (and am) infected with the horse virus. Today I am the proud owner of my very first (real) horse: Royelle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
